[
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "In the early days, disputes on the island were settled through ___________ and negotiation.",
      "Answer": "mediation"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "As the population grew, conflicts became more ___________, requiring the need for a formal government.",
      "Answer": "complex"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "The islanders decided to create a ___________ in which power is vested in elected representatives.",
      "Answer": "republic"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "The government created a navy of ___________ to defend against potential invasions.",
      "Answer": "ships"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "A new tax system, the ___________ tax, was introduced to finance the governmentâ€™s ventures.",
      "Answer": "trade"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "To prevent government overreach, the islanders created a ___________ that clearly defined the powers of the Senate.",
      "Answer": "constitution"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "The ___________ was appointed to ensure that the constitution was upheld and prevent abuse of power.",
      "Answer": "senator-in-chief"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "The government wisely chose to ___________ a portion of tax revenue for unforeseen circumstances.",
      "Answer": "reserve"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "The concept of ___________ government was a radical idea at the time, similar to the founding of modern democracies.",
      "Answer": "limited"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "The islanders recognized that taxes, while necessary for public services, reduced the amount of ___________ available for private investment.",
      "Answer": "capital"
    }
  ]
  